See how happy we all are
together.
Why?  BJP has got 239 seats brother.
Who will write the future,
who will pay its price?  The threads of a dark tomorrow are in my hands.   There was
noise of hope all around.
[Music]
They have 239 seats in the Lok Sabha.  Meaning there
is no limit to happiness.  I was thinking that
I had said so much for Rs 350.
Currently they have 239 or 240 seats.
What should I say now?  What is left to say
?  So then I opened my drafts.
I said I will see
what I was not able to say at 350.  Now there was one more thing in the
event of which we all were a part.  Non-
consensually.  Which was Ambani's son's
wedding.
Ambani first gave us the data and then said,
look my
son, and I mean Ambani is not a businessman
brother, he meant he gifted a forest to his son,
who gifts a forest
[music],
he gave the forest to his son and said,
look son, there are animals bigger than you in the world, the
son is such that he is not even able to see.   There
is no quality in it.  The son is
calling the journalists.  Come come come here.
Look at my forest.  Look at this, my
elephant.  Don't fear God, fear memes.
okay brother.  God is with you.  The public will definitely
make memes.  He is not worried,
he is doing something different.  This country
is unemployed.  The hashtag is running the country's
wedding.
All the Bollywood people came again to the country's wedding, Ambani's wedding.
Everyone was seated in one bus.  He
said in the bus, let's sit in the bus and go.  Then
people came from outside.  Ed Sheeran Aaja Rehna Come Diljit
Aaja.  Come all the singers, actors and Bollywood people.
Come sit down everyone, sit down, you have sat down, are you comfortable,
we will
dance now, that was the most expensive version, son, a
guest has come to the house,
okay friends, do your business, leave dancing to the one who knows how, poor
Ambani's son was tired, he was finally dancing in such a way that
I felt that two people in green clothes behind must be
waving his hands.
After the marriage in the Ambani family, he
sent his son to watch the Olympics.  He fell
asleep while watching.  Hey, a lot of sudden
activity is happening in front of his eyes,
poor guy.  A lot is moving.
I am getting tired.   The
poor guy fell asleep.  These people have just gone to a wedding.  There are many
things to talk about.  Different types
of food, decorations, so many things to talk about.
But people go there and
talk about the same topic which should be avoided.
How the couple looks together.
Leave it for once.
People are busy there too.  The couple looks amazing
together.
[Music]
Amazing Sat Sinha ji, there is no symmetry there.
That poor girl walked 1.5 km.
You can count his bones.  Ambani's son's
elbow is not visible.
I am fat.  Ok.  I don't believe in
body shaming.  Till you loose an elbow.
Are you [ __ ] lost an elbow like?  The
doctor came for knee replacement surgery.
Asking where
is Nee?  Don't feel bad for him.
His father has a GDP of 2-3%.
He has opened a 20-storey hospital.
Because he also knows it.  He will also have to be
given saline.  So the entire hospital will be engaged in finding the vein.
This is not the job of one or two doctors.
Sir, it has been three days since I am unable to find the vein.
Hi what's your name man
nice.  What do you do man?  What do you do?
Tech Journalist What's happening in tech in India
?  What do you report?  Ola's scooter got
burnt here.
How Technology Failed.
What more will you report, friend?  It is not
happening, that is the problem.  It is
China's problem.  A lot of tech is
happening there.  Yes.  Recently, China created an AI app called
Deep Sea which caused the stocks of big companies to fall by 10%.
So we had
no innovation other than AstroTux.  So what are you writing there
?  Devotees are writing for your information.
China has only one party system and no
opposition.
Oh right.  The opposition is stopping private companies
from doing anything innovative.  That Ola guy is
sitting there saying that I will make a good AI.
Then Rahul Gandhi comes and takes his
laptop and throws it away.  He is doing very innovative
work.  My
father did not bring the laptop for innovation.  Ok?  Some
other businessman is sitting here, I will do something innovative.
Kejriwal presses the pieces from below and
will innovate.  Innovation can happen only in a one party system.
Ok?
These people write like this, meaning logic, how will you answer
this that there is only one party in China
and there is no opposition.  That's why he has come.
So democracy is not coming in between them.  That
's right, tech journalist.  So you just
report on how we are not technologically
savvy Indian businessmen don't even agree that they are doing the wrong thing like look at that
Ola guy for
example what was I saying that
he got angry, it's simple brother you make two wheelers,
both its wheels are not
working, he is saying come here and work with me, we will
build India together, first
what is this businessman's fetish of building India
?  A decent bike is not being made.
He will make India now.  Keep
your aspirations within limits, friend.  Then
recently it launched new colours of the bike.  Who
knows, it might work in a different colour.
Need a detox.  There the boot is running.  And it is
installed there.  I will give you the money.
Hey, give it to those who are asking for a refund.
I am not tweeting about it right now because
people are blaming me.
Because of you, the
stocks I bought dipped.
I'm saying I wrote my tweets.
He wrote his tweets.
I have not accepted the job offer from Ola.
Because this Ola controversy happened.
After that I think many thousands of people
tagged me and sent me their bike number, JC
number, photo copy of service book,
they are DMing me saying, Bhaiya look at me
[music]
leave everything else, Bhaiya look at me,
what can I do brother,
when the agencies formed
for consumer protection are not able to do anything,
they go to the owner of Ola and
show him their photo with Modi ji.  She reverses and goes back.
What can I do
?  But there were some among them who had abused
me a lot earlier.
Why doesn't the bastard dog die?  Go to Pakistan.
The day I see it, I will rub it.
Then below that was my Ola, you should see.
Like, for a 500 rupee bike you left your ego,
your
opinion, everything.  Now do you understand
how people ruled for so many years?
Some Babar has come, you are shouting from here, Babar is as
good as a tree.  He said he would give 50-yard
plots to
everyone.  Babar
sir, are you married?
This joke '350 pe agar main
mara' is another new thing going viral online.  I don't know
you guys have noticed it men's rights
activists don't reduce men's
rights.  Fight for Men's Rights.  At
first I thought he was eating someone's feet.
Then I came to know that actually
people are fighting for the rights of men.  And the
biggest thing in that is that men are not expressing their feelings.
Not from now, but from a long time ago.  Okay, so on
whose feelings did the First Old War take place
?  Tarla Dalal threw stuffed brinjals in Hiroshima and Nagasaki.   And
whose feelings is he following today?  Are
Putin and Zheltkov's wives fighting
?  Without expressing, we brought this world
here.
You want to express
yourself.  And they never did anything to help women.
Men overall.
Indian men have not even thought about
what helping a woman means?  What is this nonsense?
Who is bringing all this into our culture?
Whatever things have been made in the world, women
may be using them today, but they were made
when men went to fight with each other.  When they had to
cook food themselves, then all these things came into existence like
refrigerator,
microwave, washing machine, gas stove, cooker, our
entire country is bigger than our engineers.
What is it, throw a stone in India and an
engineer will
hit it.  Country engineers are engineers.
They did not make mixers.  What is a
mixer?  There is a maker, there are three blades.  Did not
make it.  If it comes from Japan, it will come.
Grandmother died due to arthritis while grinding spices.
Grandfather is standing in the corner and saying that I find
taste only in ground spices.  I
swear, when the mixer came to the house, people came to
know that grandmother also talks.  The
grandmothers' software was updated in one day.  The mixer came and I got free for 3 hours,
grandmother is talking now.  Have you seen that
meme that comes on every WhatsApp group?  In which there are
two types of rotis.  There is a
burnt roti.  It is written on it: Love
Marriage.  The second roti is puffed.  It is
written on it that it is arranged marriage.  Look, love
marriage is like burnt bread.  Arranged marriage puffed
bread.  Even in their version of love,
even in blind love, it is the women who are making the bread.   Have you ever
seen such blind love?
Life for women is 0.75 percent better in South India.  Like
because there's rice?   You can make it
once, eat it twice or die.
Take it, leave
it.  The bread should be puffed up.
Sir, what have you done today?  I have just
come back after waving saffron on my badge.
So I thought I will eat puffed bread today.
We have won.  Firstly, he did
not create anything.  If someone is using it then we will get involved in
it.
Microwave Fridge
Washing Machine.  Once the clothes go into the washing machine, the
food goes into the fridge, nor does
heating the food in its microwave
make the nutrition completely hard.
Ok.  How do you
know?  Your degree is MA in Hindi Literature.
How do you know that the microwave sucks?   I
swear to God, the condition of women in this country is
so bad that you can just ask any woman randomly,
ma'am, I am giving you a time machine.
Where will you go?  She will say that we
cannot go back.  The situation was very bad.  After
seeing these idiots, I don't feel like going ahead.
I will stay here.
You take the time
machine.  If you have a roti maker, please
give it to me.  Give men a time machine.
He left logic behind.  Give men a
time machine.  Will start roaming around.  Where are
you going?  I am going.
To watch the 83 World Cup.  Won't you think who is paying for the ticket
?  Who will give the visa?  How will the car fare come?
Where is the passport?  I will go to watch the 83 World Cup.
Hey, I will go to
watch that Sharjah match in 1996.  Hey go I'm going to
see the demolition of 92.  For the first time someone told me that he was
giving me a time machine.  I too became
romantic with the idea.  I was
like I also want to travel.  And the man
is okay to go behind.  The situation has always been the same for us.
Ok?  I just want to travel back to 1970s India.
Because that's why India was good, friend.
Whatever I have read about it.
Like it's a beautiful time.  There were
no roads, no tolls.  There
were less vehicles.  I mean it was a train only.   Sit
wherever you are in a train.  Went somewhere, got off.
Get off at some station.
Looking at someone he said, is this some tea, sisterfucker?
[Applause]
This is some tea.
No wonder the wife left me.
And who is this
child with him?  He will become bald when he grows up.
This joke that I understood
[appreciation]
cannot be angry.
And the one who can get angry cannot file an FIR.
Who is this joke
about?  Who knows?
Your guess is as good as mine.
Meaning, rich people in India are of a certain type.
An Ambani type very mean
shameless lowly person who is another rich person who becomes rich
but acts like he is middle class.
One of the greatest
women among them is Sudha
Murthy.  He is the epitome of simplicity.  His
claim is that I am simple.  And he has
written 50 books on his simplicity.
Go to every airport and you will
find a section on Sudha Murthy.  And the point of every book is that
it is simple.  The
point of every story of his life is that he is simple.
Every story of his will be like this.  Once I went to
a mango seller.  Mango seller gave me 8 mangoes
for
₹100.  Then one lady came in corporate
attire.  Mango seller gave her eight mangoes for
₹150.  Then I went to Mango Cellar.  I ask
mango seller why you give me cheaper
mango?  We are idiots.
Someone will go and
ask the shopkeeper.  Brother, why did you give it to us at a cheaper price
?  The day was ruined.
I simply went to the mango seller.   The
mango seller told me that lady has a modern
corporate job in this international company
called
Infosys Now you are understanding
why Narayan Murthy wants to work for 70 hours
Sudha Murthy must be burning his brain I am
simple I am simple I am simple
Narayan Murthy I am outside the house
after listening to Sudha Murthy's stories friend just two
years ago she was the mother-in-law of the entire UK friend what kind
of simplicity is
this is this simplicity she is going to Rajya Sabha now
she is
simply Diwali is happening there is 1200
QI pollution there is everything your
grandfather's lungs are burning
people are bursting crackers there.  The doctor is
writing on the prescription that brother,
leave Delhi.
Your health is not good.
Stay out of Delhi for four months.  And these people are saying that
we will burn crackers.  Everyone should know that
Diwali has arrived.  I know she has come.   I am getting
leave.  It has arrived.  No no,
we will tell the Muslims that Diwali has come.
Muslims are making us listen to Coke Studio.
We are calling them bombs in return.  So if
he also starts thinking like this then there will be a
problem.
Tell me, our festival has come.
What Weird
Fetish?  People are dying.  What happened if his lungs got burnt
?  We will burn firecrackers.  Then
Delhi's socialites will come and say don't
burn crackers.  Why not burn it?  Pollution?
No, no, my
dog.  Sister
[ __ ].  What will he think about your dog
?  You think he has
empathy for the dog.  His arguments are like this.
This dog will be restless in the next six hours.  The
dog will bark.  This is the problem of
rich people.  What does he do the rest of the day?   The
dog will remain confused.
Animals are the ones who get confused.  We too are confused sometimes.
No one cares if the dog remains confused, friend.  They just feel
that these people will develop
empathy for animals.  Leave aside all these things like human being, Muslim,
minority.  Seeing the photo of the dog will
awaken emotions in their mind.  Then they will
not burn these crackers.  This is possible.  They do
n't care about anything that they do,
like what happened in the whole world,
pandemic came, what happened in India,
grand
festival, something is coming from outside, it is ready,
where did Covid come from, by flight, when was the international
lockdown imposed in the whole country, I do
n't know the logic, when asked the answer, he said that I am doing Thali
Tali
activity at 5:00 pm.  Sisterfucker,
what will be the impact of this activity?  Someone
analyzed it.  459 I was in my balcony to
see who would come to my house when the riots would happen.  There was
a crow's nest there.  Ok.
459 That crow's confidence that we will
see what
life is.  There is no worry about anything.
I will make this child clear UPSC.
I will send this one abroad.  At 5:00 the plates started ringing again.  The
crow kept flying.  He felt that he had become a fool in the area.   It
is a city issue.  There has been some problem in the state.
This country is wrong.  He went to Dubai with a golden visa.  Haven't
returned yet.  There is trauma in
them.  You can take the plate and all this in front of any crow.  He
will say, keep me away
from this brass world.
Dangerous.
Why did this event happen?  What did it happen for?  When will you be back
?  When humans themselves do not have the answer to this
, then where will the crow find it from?  Then Modi
ji said, Virat Hindu Modi ji, one man Hindu
Modi ji.  Best Hindu Modi ji.  There is
no bigger Hindu than him.  He
sent people across the country in April to collect lamps.
In the off season.   Let
me tell you now to go and bring Dandiya.   While
searching for the lamp, people got Covid
[praise].  Ca
n't take candles.  Jesus will come directly.
Candles are a mess with my faith.
I will not take the candle.
Or this happened, this was a pandemic where people are dying.  The
world is going to be sad.  Here the men
entered the kitchen.  I touched the utensils.  My
wife is having an epileptic attack.
What are you going to do today?  Then after that
Modi ji went out and spoke for 5 minutes.  He
played for 20 minutes.  I have got a chance.  Let's do some
cultural things together.  The problem is that
our no means is Diver's Faith.  You
can say anything that is Hinduism.
Anything that means I was 16 years old so I did
not eat non-veg.  Ok?  Do not eat non-veg on Tuesday.
Then when you grow a little bigger, you
can eat it after 12:00 o'clock.
Then it grew bigger.  So he said, is it
Tuesday or Wednesday here, it
is Tuesday somewhere else and Monday somewhere else,
Hindus are not creatures of one time zone,
they just roam around like free birds and
Muslims are fixed brother, they
are fixed in the syllabus, ask them any question, they will never get
angry, they are roaming in the same field
these days, brother has asked a good
question, ask any Muslim man
what is Halal, he will tell you the whole story, see
this is the system of Halal.  This is our, you know, this is what our
religious textures say.  This
is Peeta speaking.  This is what we say.  This is what the doctor
says.  This is what science says.  This is what Hazin
says.  Hindu is saying in it that
you have said enough.  Keep
some peace.  The waiter came to take the order.  Jhatka
Biryani.  Who needs to be shocked?  Jhatka Veg
Biryani.
Cut potatoes in one go.  I won't let it happen without him.  I get
stressed.
Hindu man means you can sell anything
to any Hindu man.  So many
fake products came
into our lives in the name of religion.
Tell me about electric incense sticks.
[Applause]
This is playing with my faith.  The puja is taking place in the
morning.  Smoke is not coming out.   I ca
n't see the electricity.  How will it look to
you?
I understand the point of using electric incense sticks in the morning.   I still do
n't understand it.  But
someone sold it and we took it.  Or I think save
Hinduism from
Hindus.  They are a problem.  And
80% of the country is Hindu phobic, they are
talking about Hindus, there is Hindu phobia here, I
mean if you enter Haldiram, you will start
shouting that there is Bhujia phobia brother, all the
people who have come here
are against Bhujia, these people, after taking money from George Soros,
want to end the tradition of Bhujia, they want Bhujia to become a
past, is there any logic in this thing,
but you will find Indians in every country and
in this country every Indian is saying the same thing.
Hindus have only one country, son, where should we
go?
You went everywhere.  Have you left any space
?  Someone is calling me from Africa saying
that I have to do a show.  Who am I speaking
to?  I do shows in Hindi.  Are the
Africans learning?  He accepted
that his ancestors were Sanatanis.   No no
sir there is our Indian community
sir Hindi speaking I was like which
community is it what is it doing
there Gujarati in Africa
oh thousands then I googled Gujarati
in Indian
[music]
army if they had 350 seats this other one does
not do it in Google at all.
What is the use of knowledge that you cannot share?
Friend, something will have to be done about the old people.
As long as the old people of this country
are free.  Hey friend, there is a way to give freedom.  There should be
a way to take it also.
Retire from everything.  Retire from voting.
You are 65 years old.  Why
go to vote now?  Whose future should I choose
?  Sit here comfortably.  Look at the 18 to 65
step count.  Ok?  Word count after 65.
Grandpa is from 6 to 7:30.  You will get mobile for
minutes.  And you can talk 9000 words.   It is
not more possible than that.  No.
After that
Damsharaj.  I have spoken enough.  I will have to do it friend.  If you want to
give rights to someone, you will have to take rights from someone else.
Yes, take it for the old people.
What do you do?  Well, it is of no use.
This is the same thing that happened, apply turmeric.  Hey
sisterfucker, this turmeric, ashwagandha, all this existed only
when there was no medical science.  Paracetamol I.
Undid everything.
Take paracetamol now, what's in it?   The
old men are busy.  Apply turmeric,
apply sandalwood.  It's stress, old man.
Yes, this is the big chunk of tax payer,
old man.  And the one who seems to be the most learned among the old men, if
you
see him then you will feel that no friend Anand
Mahendra is also old.  He
tweets well.  Read his tweets carefully sometime.
Thermodynamics, Marine Biology and Meaning
Radioactivity.  How to improve your car.
Apart from that, brother has talked on every topic.
AI goes to meet.  People
call him sarcastically, he comes seriously.
Anand Mahindra tweets anything,
man.  Once there was a flood
in Mumbai which we call the Spirit of Mumbai.  It is
called the Spirit of Mumbai
because some people die.
Hence the Spirit of Mumbai.  So
what's happening at Spirit of Mumbai?  There has been a flood.
Double decker bus swinging in water.  Ok
?  The kids are going over it.  Summer salt is
killing the water.  Ok?  You
can reach Sri Lanka directly by flowing.
There Anand Mahindra gets the video.
We feel that he is a wise man.   He
will say, hey kids, what are you doing?  Do not do it.
Where is the administration?  It should not happen.
Why doesn't anyone stop these children
?  Anand Mahendra writes there When
Life Gives You Lemons.
This country's scholar has been fooled.
What is left to save then
?  Then he talks like this, life gives you
lemon.  AI says at the meeting that we will
create Indian AI.  Hey, you haven't
made anything Indian yet.  One day you will suddenly come and make everything right.  It
is not possible.  You know, the
less I say about Indian businesses, the
better.  Whenever I speak something happens.
I have decided that why should I offend
people only in one art
form why when I can use another art
form so with a huge round of applause welcome
my music buddy for today Kabir Singh
yes or he is Kabir Singh if Karan Johar is the
director many lagta hai sweet aadmi ladkiyan
ki baat sunta hai nonsense galat
desh mein janm ho gaya.
Our first song is on two very
independent institutions of India, ED and
CBI.  Earlier the judge used to say that there is a
parrot and myna locked in the cage.  Then Modi ji came in 2014, the
great Hindu.  He said, what is this
we have?  Why have they been closed?
Why are their hands closed?  Open them.  Yes.   Do
not open the cage.  Just open your hands.
Earlier they were locked in a cage.  Now
cameras are being shot from inside the cage.
Is this what they are doing?
What did they do in Maharashtra?  Ed was able to do what the
missionaries couldn't.
Change of heart.  You were thinking of one thing.  ED has come to
your house.  I am thinking about something else right now.
Poor Pope, while calculating in Watkin, got busy
that he is investing money in India
, he is building hospitals, he has given ice, he has given
schools, he has given St. Claus, he has given gifts
, he has given Bible.  All the Hindu people said it is with them.
Yes.  We don't want it.  Give everything else.  That's all
fine.  Our first song is on the independence of CBI and ED.   Let's
go.
If CBI comes after you or ED troubles you, come to me my
dear,
why should you be afraid?
If CBI comes after you or ED troubles you, come to me my
dear, why should you be afraid? Why should you be
afraid? My party is
obedient to the corrupt Sangh, whoever gets his hand on his head, the
charge sheet becomes blank. Listen, listen, hey
son, listen, the big leaders of this party, listen, listen, hey
son, listen, the big leaders of this party, be it a
murderer or a rapist,
all get bail here. Why should you be afraid? Why should you be afraid?
If CBI comes after you or ED troubles you, come to me my
dear, why should you be afraid? Why should you be afraid? Be it a
lawyer or an inspector, judge or
collector, everyone bows before you, including
press reporter, if they just shake hands once, they can
hide their sins. Why should they be afraid?
Why should they be
afraid? Think about what has happened in this country, ED, CBI,
judiciary, the poor judges are sitting and making rules for Dream 11.
How will this be in this country, nothing will happen, we do
not discuss that.
You can make a team on Dream 11 only once. It is
written in the judge's order that he  It has been done
with the Maharashtra elections, brother, you will have to
tell what they did here first,
Shiv Sena came out of BJP,
then Shiv Sena came out of Shiv Sena.
NCP came out of NCP.
Nine buttons were given to one voter.
Everyone got confused.  It was started by one person.
Thane is a very good district in Mumbai, I come from there.
Police station rickshaw,
beard on the face, glasses in the eyes
Police station rickshaw, beard on the face,
glasses in the eyes, gives a glimpse, sometimes
hides in a cave.  If you look at it from my perspective,
he appears to be a traitor, a police station rickshaw, a
car on the
face, glasses
on the eyes, oh he is not a minister, he is a party hopper and what can be said, he makes a hole in the plate from which he eats, he gets more in Fadnas' lap than in the ministry, he has got a bow and arrow, he has got my father, he wants this, a police station rickshaw, a beard on the face, glasses on the eyes, oh
think about it, this is politics, we had to
end their nepotism, we stole someone's father,
what will be the reply brother, if I meet
Tendulkar's son tomorrow, I will tell him to come brother, let's meet for lunch for
half an hour, I will praise Tendulkar
and say, see, from today onwards, he is my
father.
You find someone on the way.
Our third song is about this loot going on The
whole country is busy digging We are digging We do
n't know if we might find something Dig keep digging You will find Starbux under the Udappi You will
find Udappi under the Starbux
Your tax money is going to waste The
government has come to ruin these roads The
metro is in their mind Jump and take a
stretch This is to
increase the traffic This is to
demolish the bridges This is what they
call it
[Music]
Dictatorship and nothing else matters Just
your aspirations have gone into the dustbin
Corporate employees will pay more taxes than the corporates This is happening
in the interest of the country brother The country's interest There is
so much inflation in the country with the government The
loot of the people has earned The saree-clad sister has come To
steal the salaries This is to
suppress the middle class This is to
feed popcorn This is what they
call it Nirmala Tai
She is the JNU student The country
deserves.
Take it brother, it is Nehru's mistake.
Studied at the wrong university.  If she had
studied in Banaras Hindu University, she would have been a good Finance
Minister.
Now similarly Donald Trump is going to
send Indians back to the golden era.
I have spent a month around the airport.
Whoever comes, I will say
welcome back to Modi's
India.  It's very good.  You are saying it was
very nice.  Now let's see how we
enjoy.  We will build a developed
India together.  Another anthem of developed India
We will be
poor We will be
poor We will be poor One
day superstition in the mind
Destruction of the country We will be
poor One
day we will be naked Riots all around
Police troubles all around One
day
Nathura movement Asaram in the mind We will be poor One
day there will be cow propaganda We will be weapons in hands
Sangh's etiquette One
day people
unemployed On the verge of poverty
We will be poor One day I can see it or
two equal to $86
Soon Hey brother the golden age of India has just arrived Right now
we are looking for something in every Chief Minister
Today there is a Chief Minister We are looking for something
So let's go for that When I
saw the Chief Minister it felt like When I
saw the Chief Minister it felt like
Gujarat was burning Like the night in Manipur Like hateful
words As if you have distributed notes As if you have snatched votes As if there is
evil in the mind As if you have
forgotten the promises made to us after taking votes
[Music] When I
saw the Chief Minister it felt like the
mind was black As if you have looted money As if the colour was saffron As if you have company As if you have
conflict in the party As if you have
sold the country As if there is one poisonous thing in the Parliament
Chhote Phatta
[Praise]
is our last song today
on the most important man of the country, this song is on the
fickle character of our Modi ji,
first he wasted 20 years in one-sided hatred for
an Italian woman,
now he is going to waste the next 20 years in one-sided love for an
Italian woman.
Modi is following Miloni ji with a pizza pan.   I am
teaching them Dhokla Pizza.
Hey, Modi ji is in love brother.  Every
night at 1:30 am with Meloni on Jio
network.   Is
Ayodhya a tableau?  There is still room left.
Meloni is asking Modi ji.  Who are
you?  Who are you
Narendra?  Modi ji is saying one nation one
performer.  I will tell you by singing.
I am a liar.  I am also a murderer.  I am
also involved in mixing everything up.   I am a
liar and I am also a murderer.  Mix everything up,
I am also included.
Stealing MP Pressing Vices Stealing MP.
My only
fault is suppressing voices.  He does not go back on his promises.   I never
complete them.  Dictator oh
dictator oh dictator oh dictator oh dictator oh dictator oh dictator oh dictator The chores will
sing along with us Audience should also take some
responsibility
Everyone raise your hands and say I
consent to
comedy one two three It is
good I am a Dokla, I am a Khokla
too I eat Dhokla everyday
Stealing schemes and claiming them to be yours Stealing schemes and claiming them to be yours This is
my only fault
I don't show my degree I don't appoint anyone's job
Dictator oh dictator Dictator oh dictator Dictator oh dictator There are
my own sycophants everywhere
Only my name is raised above the corpses My career is
behind Amit Shah's
story seems true I like Meloni The
false story seems true I like Meloni
Making fools by making utensils
banging Fooling people by making utensils banging This is
my only
fault I have no relation with the poor No
one can escape from ED.
Ja oh da oh
da thank you so much
[applause]
Ja
and ya I'm gonna put this show up on
YouTube at some point and ya and for all of
the people who will not like this show.  I'll just have
something for you.  Or this is for all
engineers I am people This is the
Constitution of
India This is what allows me to do What I do
and in the framework of this book you
can feel free to do anything Thank you so much
Breath sitting behind Price of electricity of WiFi
When even God is a subscription Name of whose
sweat Whose blood New scales Sold
coin Whatever is said is the truth Here the voice of the labourer is
suppressed Here glass towers speak in the air The
poor are on the ground Their dreams are also clear Here the gods of Algo
do business here No one
listens to the labourer Here even the mother cries where the rivers burnt The
owners of the fields themselves There was gold under the soil The
soil has now become a wound Don't forgive the debt of the poor Re Re Re Re Re